Thank you for watching!
Good evening to everyone here at the Tachikawa Stage Guide!
Good evening!
Now, let me introduce to you the new members who have passed the audition for new members of Hello! Project 25th Anniversary New Member Audition and will be joining Tsubagi Factory.
Please come in!
Congratulations!
Please introduce yourself.
I am Miho Ishii, a 15-year-old junior high school student from Kanagawa Prefecture.
My favorite angle is 90 degrees, and my least favorite angle is 22 degrees.
I look forward to working with you!
I'm Yu Murata, a 13-year-old junior high school student from Aichi, Japan.
My favorite hairstyle is the ponytail I'm wearing now.
I look forward to working with you.
I'm Fuuka Doi, a 13-year-old 2nd year junior high school student from Osaka, Japan.
My favorite language of flowers is Kaede.
I would like to make precious memories together with you all, which is the language of maple.
I look forward to working with you.
And now, we have decided the member color of the new members.
So, then, please introduce me from Mihane-chan.
My member color is white.
My member, I, Yu Murata's member color is light pink.
Yes, I'm MURATA MURATA.
My member, I, Doifuka's member color is Bright Green.
The three schools have joined Tsubaki Factory and will work together from now on.
Please continue to support the new Tsubaki Factory.
Thank you for watching.
Haloste, this time with Rin Kawana of Angelem and Juice Juice's connection with each other.
Please stay with us until the end, as we will be presenting this time with these two.
Hello Project 2024 Winter 3 of As is currently underway!
We, Angulum, Juice Juice, and Tea Horse are performing together as Team B and touring together.
There are a lot of episodes, aren't there?
One of my episodes was when Rin Kawana was close to her bite during rehearsal.
After Rin Kawana's solo part was over, she was heaving all by herself.
Yes.
How embarrassing.
I thought I heard it in my ears, but when we repeated the song, I heard it over and over again, so I thought it was Rin saying it.
I remember I was so surprised when I asked her if she heard me say "hee".
I was really struggling with the solo part of the song, and I couldn't sing it well at all.
I was struggling with the solo part of the song, and I couldn't sing it well at all, but during rehearsal when I was singing through the microphone, I was so surprised.
I was so surprised.
Sleepy
Rhythm
about the rhythm
Mr. Matsunaga gave us some advice
I was so happy to hear that.
That made me so happy.
I was like...
I said, "Okay, I'll do it.
In the back of this note
When I was saying, "If you listen here, it will be easier to sing...
And he told me...
What?
Yes, sir.
You told me.
That made me very happy.
And thanks to your advice
I've been able to sing better because of your advice.
I really appreciate it very much.
I'm glad.
Thank you very much.
Now, please watch this video.
Please enjoy!
Nana Nana Nana
me
I'm so frustrated!
I'm so frustrated that my childhood friend Kikki Kikki didn't get me.
Now everyone is the hostess's bait.
Why is that? When did that happen?
How did that little character get away?
She's the messiah, the savior, the rage seeker...
She's just a monster. She's a fixture.
Why is that so?
It's time to introduce her.
Why, why, why, why?
I mean, why is it working so well?
How did it work?
I'm so frustrated.
She's trying to act cool...
I actually hate to lose.
I hear rumors.
I hear that.
But there's no point in being impatient.
Let's work steadily and steadily.
You're a crude little shit.
I'll say it to myself.
I'll tell myself that...
Wait a minute!
Wait a minute.
I'm okay
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
I'm okay I'm okay I'm okay
I'm just the same age as that model
What a guy. He looks so different.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm okay
Oh, now it's come to this
I'm going to do something that's not so expensive
Or maybe we'll just hit them over the head with the highest price we can find.
Why?
You're not afraid?
Why, why, why?
I mean, it's all part of the exercise, it's all part of the skill
You take chances, you lose yourself in the end
But when you see they beat you to it...
I can't do anything good yet.
Feelings I'm sure I'm sure I'm helpless I comfort myself
I feel like I'm too late, like I don't even have my hands on it. Wait a minute.
Oh yeah!
But, I can't help it, I'm sweating.
It's not a steady, steady job
It's a lie.
I'll tell myself I've noticed
But I feel like I can't do something.
I'm frustrated. I'm cajoled.
If you can do it, it means you're not done yet.
It means I'm okay, I can do it.
I console myself.
What is it?
Punktata.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Ah, I'm so disappointed in you
Ah I'm so frustrated
I'm so frustrated
Challenge en chew everyting
Rin Kawana of Angulum and
Rin Kawana of Angeleum and Riai Matsunaga of JuiceJuice present Hello Step.
We'd like to talk a little bit about each other from here.
I'm going to ask you some questions.
So please answer them quickly and without thinking too much.
Yes, I'll do my best.
What are you personally interested in right now?
Working as a music director.
What would you like to do with JuiceJuice members now?
Strawberry picking
The date of this delivery, February 14, is
Risa Imii's first photo book was released!
Please give us your guesses from the members.
Her smile is so cute!
What do you do on your day off?
Sleeping or watching live videos.
This June marks the 5th anniversary of JuiceJuice's second year!
Looking back, what has left the biggest impression on you?
Talking with Mr. Miyamoto this time.
Story
There are so many things that are on my mind.
I want to ask them all.
The first thing that caught my attention was
Looking back on the 5th anniversary since you joined JuiceJuice, what was the most memorable moment for you?
what was the most memorable moment for you?
You said it was the talk with Mr. Miyamoto.
That's right.
Before I joined JuiceJuice
I really admired Miyamoto as a manager.
That's right.
Even after I joined JuiceJuice
I'm very much interested in sticking to Miyamoto-san.
I'm very concerned about it.
There are so many of them.
During the rehearsal for the concert where Ms. Miyamoto was graduating
I hit a bit of a wall.
I was in the middle of the rehearsal studio with Mr. Miyamoto.
We talked for about an hour.
We talked about all kinds of things.
That's what I remember most.
What did you talk about?
At that time, Yume Kudo and I were the youngest members of JuiceJuice.
I was trying my best to keep up with the older members.
I didn't want to follow them.
I wanted to compete in the same ring with them.
I asked Mr. Miyamoto for advice on what I should do to achieve this.
I asked Mr. Miyamoto what I should do to make that happen.
He gave me a very sincere answer.
I'm still doing my best with those words in my heart.
Next, I was curious about a question that I thought of.
What do you do on your days off?
I really love sleeping.
When I sleep, the day is over.
The day is really over.
It's true.
I'm often doubted.
When I wake up, the day is really over.
I was skeptical.
Really?
Mr. Matsunaga once asked me...
What do you do on your day off?
He said I was sleeping.
Sleeping?
I really think so.
I'm taking this opportunity to ask you.
You really do sleep.
It's done.
That's great.
So we'll ask Rin Kawana a question after the VTR.
Hallo! Sta!
Getchu!
Shanwi dance!
Is it because of the summer?
Bach-chang, bach-chang, bach-chang, bach-chang, bach-chang, bach-chang...
Drink your tea!
We are
First Album
CHANNEL 1 is now on sale!
Hallo! STE!
Next, I would like to ask Rin Kono a question from me!
I'll do my best.
A month and a half after the new year started
What kind of goods are you going to replace in 2024?
Gama-guchi pouch
It's been a little over two months since I turned 20.
What is the moment when you realize you are in your 20s?
Medical questionnaire
What do you want to do with the members of ANGELUM now?
Go to the beach
What is your favorite Juice Juice song?
In the middle of romance
2024 is Rin Kono's 4th year in Angulum
Looking back, what do you remember most?
The engine before the live.
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
What is the moment when you realize that you are in your 20s?
The medical questionnaire.
When you write down how old you are.
I knew...
I think about it when I write my age because the decimal place has changed from 1 to 2.
I still think about it when I write my age.
Also, in a little questionnaire
When I circled "20s" on the questionnaire
When I circled "20s", I thought I was in my 20s.
I circled it while thinking that I was in my 20s.
I circled it, thinking that I was in my 20s.
It's the moment when I feel it the most.
I'm looking forward to it!
It's coming so fast!
And my favorite Juice Juice song is
In the middle of romance
Yes!
Why not!
I already love the bouncy song
It's called "Ben Ben Ben Ben Ben Ben Ben
Before we started filming...
I was talking with Mr. Matsunaga about "Ben Ben Ben Ben Ben" before the shooting of the cat started.
I really love it.
I sing this song when I go out for karaoke.
I also love this song when I see Juice Juice's performance.
It's a song that really moves me when I see Juice Juice perform it.
Thank you very much!
Thank you so much! Stay tuned for more after this!
Thank you for watching!
This is Natsuyaki Kimiyami. Here we go. Hello Kitchen. This time, we have this member here.
Yes, please. I am Yutano Sato from Beyonce Seasonings. I'm Yutano Sato of Beyonce Seasonings, and it's nice to meet you.
I have been given the unit name "Seasonings," so I will do my best in cooking.
I look forward to working with you, Mr. Sato.
I look forward to working with you.
What would you like to make this time?
I would like to make a chiffon cake.
Sweets.
Here are the ingredients.
So, Utano, do you cook?
I do cook.
I do cook. But not this kind of cake?
I have hardly ever made cakes.
I see. Well then, let's try our best today as a challenge. I look forward to working with you.
What shall we do first?
Speaking of sweets, eggs are used, so I'll start by separating the eggs into yolks and whites.
People say I'm very dexterous.
That's not true.
Actually?
As a matter of fact, yes.
What do they say?
I like handmade things.
I like handmade things and makeup, and I make clothes.
Clothes?
You mentioned it.
It wasn't very clear.
I made a yukata.
It's an old one?
I made a yukata from a piece of cloth when I was in high school, and I love Japanese clothes.
In the future, I'll be a kimono-wearing madam.
I have to wear it.
That's cool.
I see.
When the egg yolks are light and smooth, add granulated sugar a little bit at a time.
When you make vanilla ice cream, you do it until the ice cream is white and fluffy, like blanc seals.
But with this, it's fine until it's melted.
If you mix with your left hand while mixing with your right hand...
That's right, that's right.
If you leave it in that state, it will change again.
This is actually very important, because it will separate.
Hurry up!
It's important that the oil on top of the oil makes it look a little shiny.
It's getting shiny.
And here is vanilla oil.
Vanilla oil.
You may not be familiar with it.
But with essence, the fragrance is volatilized and disappears.
With oil, it's fine.
This is also a liquid in oil, so you have to be careful here.
This first part is very important.
Do you see any hardening around here?
Are you all right with the outside?
Don't worry.
We use rice flour.
70 grams.
Yes.
And we're going to use a little baking powder.
3 grams of baking powder.
3g here
It's perfect, isn't it?
No lumps, right?
No lumps.
It's beautiful. It's so beautiful.
Yes, it's beautiful!
I want to set the oven to 180 degrees Celsius before the egg white meringue.
This is the part I'm nervous about.
I'm nervous.
Is this close by?
Yes, I have it at home.
When it starts to turn white, I'm going to put a little bit of branute in it.
I put in 60 grams of Branute.
Okay, let's make it faster.
It becomes more and more like meringue or snow, right?
Then, slow down the speed.
Then I'll slow down the speed and blend in the rough bubbles.
Yes, that's good.
First of all, take a little bit of this and put it in here.
Don't crush the bubbles too much.
Ah...
Take a little bit of this, put it in here, and try not to crush the foam.
This is the hardest part.
I'm so nervous.
Don't worry, it's okay. It's all mixed up.
Here's the point.
Once all the ingredients are mixed, switch to a spatula and mix them further.
Yes, yes...
Okay, okay.
Put this meringue here.
Yes, sir.
And then mix it with a spatula.
Yes, and then mix them together again.
Yes, from here.
Mix it all together.
Yes, this time...
Yes, all of it.
Yes, all the way through.
My right hand is getting muscular.
That's true.
I usually hold the mic with my left hand.
I'm hoping this will be enough to even things out.
Is it?
Positive.
Yeah, I was worried about my left hand.
It'll be good.
Is it going to work?
The microphone is heavy, isn't it?
I'm going to take the yellow part and put it on the white part.
It's not the yellow part, it's the yellow part.
The yellow one is just right for yellow.
If the yellow one was good, then it's yellow.
Yellow is yellow because yellow is good.
Yellow is yellow because yellow is yellow.
It's like this...
Yellow estab shift
Yellow hands are good
Yellow.
Yes, sir.
So authoritarian
Yes.
And then...
Takkyukushi
If you find a big part like this, you can mix it like this.
If you find a big part, you can mix it like this.
Grizzly, grizzly, grizzly, grizzly.
Then I'll shock it.
Then you just give it a little bit of a twist here, and then you just kind of let the air out.
One more time, one more time, I think that's good.
And then I'm going to put it in the oven.
Wow, that's it!
Yes, it's ready.
Yes, sir.
I'd like to oven for about 15 minutes from here.
First of all, Utano, you are active in BEYONDZ,
Of course, you do live performances, but you are also involved in various other activities,
I heard that you are also involved in stage performances,
How do you feel about performing on stage? How do you feel about it?
Well, BEYONDZ has been performing every year since the year of the review and every year since before the review,
Last year, we had the opportunity to perform in the "Drama Girls Club," "Biospy," and "The Missing Dash Case," a play about a spy,
It was the first time I tried my hand at action.
I have performed on stage quite a few times, yes, this kind of thing.
I had done many performances, but this was my first time doing action,
So, I started with basic exercises with my teacher,
So this is a shield, right?
That's right. A shield. Right, left, avoid.
Kick and all that.
All of it. But did you really enjoy it? Did you enjoy playing as a shield?
It was fun. I felt like I got stronger.
Indeed.
I can understand that.
I see.
Even if something happens to me now, I might be able to help you.
That's true.
The character I was playing grew up in a very difficult environment,
I was playing a role where I grew up in a tough environment and went to a neighboring country to spy on people who had a little more freedom,
Oh, really?
In the play, I was able to dress very fashionably, since it was set in a neighboring country,
I changed my facial expressions and so on to show that I was very happy about it, which I normally wouldn't be.
I changed the facial expressions and so on.
I changed their expressions, made their hair shiny, etc.
Yes, that's right.
Maybe they don't usually pay that much attention to it, but yesterday at this time, they are probably doing it nicely.
Yes, yes.
I'm not trying to be a different person.
Yes, he may let his hair down a little differently during training and when he is undercover in this neighboring country.
Wow.
That's very detailed.
Yes, it is.
I see, but I guess you have that in your mind.
It's a switch.
Yes, it is.
Is there a movie of it?
Yes, it will be released on Blu-ray this spring.
That's great.
Then, it's already on Blu-ray,
I'll watch it while thinking about your present.
You have to buy it.
You can look at anything.
I have no choice but to look at this.
Please.
Please, please, please.
So, it's been exactly 15 minutes.
Oh, there is a slight change.
It's really swollen.
It's a little cracked.
Oh, it's okay. It's okay if it's cracked.
Are you okay?
This is the right thing to do.
It's fine.
It's good.
It's perfect.
Perfect, perfect, perfect.
We're going to lower the temperature from here.
Lower it or not.
Don't open it.
160.
15 minutes.
Oh.
In 15 minutes, we'll do the whipped cream and...
I'll do the strawberries.
Ah, I see.
That's OK.
That's right.
Then let's do it here.
Okay.
So we've completed two times.
Enjoy.
Yes, I see.
Ho! Wow! It looks good! It's so beautiful! It's totally cool! Yay!
Bon appétit.
Yeah! Yum! Yeah!
Yes, Riho was so cute in her echo! It was so cute! It looks like she's going to make a delicious chiffon cake!
I can't wait to see it! I'm looking forward to it! The completion! It was like that, wasn't it! Yes!
So, let's talk about cooking. Have you cooked recently?
Recently, I've been addicted to curry, and when I get hooked on it, I tend to eat it continuously.
I've been eating curry for 3 days! What?
That's right, that's right!
So, I started to add my own seasonings to the runes on the market, and I wondered which ones were the best for curry, and how they would change the curry.
I ate 9 servings, so I did all of them.
As a result, the most delicious was the royal road!
Aah!
Yes, the store-bought runes were the best, but when I added mayonnaise at the making stage, it became, well, very mild?
Wow! Sounds delicious!
I highly recommend it!
Wow! That's amazing!
Have you used a frying pan recently?
Well, the last time I used a frying pan was when I was into konjac. I bought konjac that needed to be cooked, cut it into small pieces and stir-fried it,
At that time,
I cut the konnyaku into small pieces and stir-fried them, and then I put the konnyaku with the konnyaku cut into pieces so that the flavor would soak into the konnyaku.
Yes, yes, yes.
Then, I seasoned it with soy sauce, and the konnyaku with the cuttings became very flavorful and tasty.
I knew it.
I wondered if there was really a meaning to this, but I learned that there really is!
So, I will continue to find new ways to eat delicious food!
Haloste!
Rin Kawada from Angelem and Riai Matsunaga from JuiceJuice are presenting "Haloste!
Today is February 14, Valentine's Day.
Many of the members of JuiceJuice do a lot of cooking,
Every year on Valentine's Day, the members make chocolate candies and bring them to us,
On White Day, they return the favor by making sweets,
It is very fulfilling every year.
So today, I would like to try a little fun project.
We have written in our sketchbooks the words we would like to be said with our Valentine's Day chocolates,
We will announce the words we would like to be said to you.
Let's hear what you want to say!
Se-no! Don!
Oh!
I see!
Cute!
The word I would like to be said is "Receive.
Well, since Ms. Matsunaga is from Osaka Prefecture, I wanted her to say it in Kansai dialect, so I chose this word.
Yes, I did.
Now, I, Rin Kawana, will ask Ms. Matsunaga to say what she would like to be said with chocolate.
Please say it in a cheerful way.
Okay, here we go.
Three, two, one, please.
Take it!
Oh!
This makes me happy. It makes me feel like a friend, and I'm personally very touched.
Next, here's what I would like to be told with chocolate.
I made you some chocolate, so eat some chocotte! I've made some chocolate, so eat some chocotte!
I even threw in a pun to make it sound a little more Osaka-like,
The key point of this phrase is that there is a heart around it,
I think there's a heart around it.
Yes, I understand. I would like you to say it.
So, let's have Rin Kawana say it.
I will ask Rin Kawana to speak. Three, two, one.
I made some chocolate, so eat a little bit.
Oh! So cute! Did you see any hearts? Yes, they were. They were so big and fluttery.
It was so cute. It was cute.
This world is wonderful, isn't it? What great love it's surrounded by.
If you're here, if I think of you, that's it, this is a Wonderful World.
In the dream that's inside of you, if I think of you, that's all, this is Wonderful World.
If I had never met you, what would I be doing now?
Ordinary life, ordinary happiness, whatever.
There's no such thing.
I found it. I'm sure there's something for each of us.
Because I met you, this world is the best
You oh
ainen
Float here.
I don't like the rain that comes suddenly, but sometimes it's nice to forget something
When I see a rainbow of seven colors
Everything is coming now
I'm still shouting that I can't reach my dream
Because I met you, this world is
me
Me
me me me
Wow!
Brap-n Up!
Wow Wow Wow!
I'm sure you'll be fine as usual
Cornering of Angulum and
Ria Matsunaga of Juice Juice presents "Haloste," a show featuring Angelem cornering and Ria Matsunaga of Juice Juice.
It's time to say goodbye!
Here's an announcement!
Hello Project 2024 Winter 3 of As is now underway!
Angeleum Juice Juice is
They are performing as Team B with Tea Horse!
The next performance will be in Hyogo on February 17.
I've always had the image of Kansai's performances being very energetic.
I'm looking forward to seeing you all in Hyogo too!
And then there's Angulum Concert 2023!
Big Love Akari Takeuchi Final Live
The Blu-ray DVD of "From Angulum with love" is now on sale!
Please enjoy the wonderful scenery of the Yokohama Arena concert!
And on March 30 and 31 at Makuhari Messe
Think Carbon Neutral 2024
Bi-San Yamasakai Movement will be held at Makuhari Messe on March 30 and 31!
This is an annual event and I'm really looking forward to this year's event!
Haloste is a channel where Hello Project members will be appearing more and more!
New videos are uploaded every Wednesday, so please subscribe to the channel!
This time we have Rin Kawana from Angulum and Leah Matsunaga from Juice Juice!
Good bye!
Thank you for watching!